[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When Joe Dirt from the self-titled movie meets the girl at the carnival, who does he think she is?", "correct_answer": "his sister", "incorrect_answers": ["his best friend from school", "his cousin", "his old neighbor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "James Dean received the first official posthumous Academy Award nomination for Best Actor for his performance in this movie.", "correct_answer": "East of Eden", "incorrect_answers": ["Giant", "Trouble Along the Way", "Rebel Without a Cause"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Rowan Sebastian Atkinson was born on the 6 January 1955, in what country?", "correct_answer": "England", "incorrect_answers": ["France", "USA", "The Republic of South Africa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is the correct pairing?", "correct_answer": "oneirology - the study of dreams", "incorrect_answers": ["symbology - the study of percussion instruments", "oncology - the study of microbes", "graminology - the study of grammar"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these charming actors stars in the 2009 movie Public Enemies?", "correct_answer": "Johnny Depp", "incorrect_answers": ["John Travolta", "Brad Pitt", "Tom Cruise"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Luxembourg is bordered by all of the following nations except this one.", "correct_answer": "Netherlands", "incorrect_answers": ["Belgium", "France", "Germany"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This movie won Oscars for Best Picture, Best Original Screenplay and Best Editing at the 78th Academy Awards.", "correct_answer": "Crash", "incorrect_answers": ["Traffic", "The Aviator", "Saving Private Ryan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is the star of a show that debuted on Disney Channel in March 2006?", "correct_answer": "Miley Cyrus", "incorrect_answers": ["Lindsay Lohan", "Amanda Bynes", "Jamie Lynn Spears"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What did John Beckwith and Jeremy Grey do for a living in the great movie Wedding Crashers?", "correct_answer": "they worked together in divorce meditation", "incorrect_answers": ["they were both lawyers", "they both worked at Blockbuster Video", "they did not work, all they did was crash weddings"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The reclassification of Pluto as a dwarf planet in 2006 caused the emerging of what?", "correct_answer": "New word in English", "incorrect_answers": ["Risings among astronomy teaches in the USA", "New ethnical conflicts in the Middle East", "A sect of violent Pluto followers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "You can fry an egg on a sidewalk when it reaches how many degrees Fahrenheit?", "correct_answer": "158", "incorrect_answers": ["143", "167", "172"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Keene Act outlawed vigilantes in the Watchmen universe.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]